<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cali VIP Tours</title>
    <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cali VIP Tours</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 09:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://caliviptours.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Explore the Marvels of Cali with VIP Tours!</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/blog/blog-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/blog/blog-2/</guid>
      <description>Get ready for an incredible adventure through the vibrant city of Cali! Look no further than Cali VIP Tours – your ultimate companion for delving into the heart and soul of Colombia. Our exceptional tour services are designed to cater to travelers from all around the world, whether you hail from the USA, Europe, Asia, Latinoamerica, or any other corner of the globe. Prepare to be captivated by the charm and excitement that only Cali can offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Cali VIP Blog</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/blog/blog-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/blog/blog-1/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our blog, your window into the world of Cali VIP Tours. Step into a realm where Cali&amp;rsquo;s vibrant culture, captivating history, and unforgettable experiences come to life.
Our blog is your personal guide to uncovering the richness of Cali, guided by the expertise of Cali VIP Tours. As your companions in exploration, we&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to share insider perspectives, hidden gems, and local insights that illuminate the essence of the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Cali</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/about/</guid>
      <description>Contact usBook with usMap of Cali 
Google MapsUseful Phone Numbers in Cali  🚑 Emergency Center: 123 🚓 Police Emergency: 112 🚒 Fire Department Emergency: 119 🚗 Roadside Assistance: 124 ☎️ Cali Tourist Information: +57 2 554 0555 ✈️ International Airport (CLO): +57 2 662 6300 🏥 University Hospital of Valle: +57 2 558 1234  General Information Cali, officially Santiago de Cali, is the capital of Valle del Cauca in Colombia.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna prado - August 2023</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/testimonials/testimonial-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/testimonials/testimonial-2/</guid>
      <description>Nice to went there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antoiné Zudeikis - August 2023</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/testimonials/testimonial-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/testimonials/testimonial-3/</guid>
      <description>Very happy happened Cali times!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cali City Tour</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/cali-city-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/cali-city-tour/</guid>
      <description>Contact usBook with usWelcome to the captivating Cali City Tour, where we invite you to embark on an extraordinary journey through the heart and soul of this vibrant Colombian city. At Cali VIP Tours, our passion for exploration and discovery knows no bounds.
Discover San Antonio: Our adventure begins in the enchanting neighborhood of San Antonio. Cobblestone streets lined with colorful houses, adorned with street art, create an atmosphere that&amp;rsquo;s both charming and inspiring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cali Walking Tour DownTown</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/cali-walking-tour-downtown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/cali-walking-tour-downtown/</guid>
      <description>Contact usBook with usLet the warm heart of this city conquer you as its music and dance envelop you on this walking tour through Cali&amp;rsquo;s main sites.
The Singing City: Welcome to the thrilling Cali Downtown Walking Tour, where the vibrant essence of the city awaits you at every corner. At Cali VIP Tours, we are dedicated to providing you with a unique experience that captures the passion and vitality that make Cali an unforgettable destination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Touring Region Private Transfer</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/coffee-tour-region-private-transfer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/coffee-tour-region-private-transfer/</guid>
      <description>Contact usBook with usExperience safe and comfortable travel as you prepare for an exciting new adventure. Let us be your companions on journeys to and from Cali, as well as to or from Pereira, Armenia, Salento, or Filandia, in the heart of the coffee region.
Discover the Coffee Paradise: Welcome to the Private Transfer for Coffee Touring Region, where convenience meets exploration. At Cali VIP Tours, we prioritize your journey&amp;rsquo;s comfort and enjoyment, making every transfer an integral part of your overall experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/contact/</guid>
      <description>This is the contact page, Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   Check out Formspree for a simple, online form.
Cali VIP Tours is a project dedicated to showcasing the essence of Cali in a unique way.
Contact us for further information for assistance and booking.
Contact usBook with us</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phil Specktor - August 2023</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/testimonials/testimonial-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/testimonials/testimonial-1/</guid>
      <description>Unforgetable!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Private Salsa Lesson Experience (With Locals)</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/private-salsa-lesson-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/private-salsa-lesson-experience/</guid>
      <description>Contact usBook with usChallenge yourself and get to know Cali through its best cultural expression: Salsa! This way, you can dance and mingle with us.
Immerse in the Hot Rhythm: Welcome to the exciting Private Salsa Lesson Experience (With Locals), where Cali&amp;rsquo;s fiery rhythm becomes your guide. At Cali VIP Tours, we offer you the chance to dive into the passion and vitality of Salsa, the dance that makes the city&amp;rsquo;s heart beat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Cipriano Tour Adventure</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/san-cipriano-tour-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/san-cipriano-tour-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Contact usBook with usSan Cipriano River Adventure with Cali VIP Tours
Explore the enchanting San Cipriano with Cali VIP Tours. This tour takes you deep into the heart of the Colombian rainforest, where the San Cipriano River weaves its magic.
A Natural Paradise
San Cipriano is a hidden paradise, untouched by time. With us, you&amp;rsquo;ll journey through pristine landscapes, encounter diverse wildlife, and take refreshing dips in crystal-clear river waters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fooding Tour Alameda Market</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/the-fooding-tour-alameda-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/the-fooding-tour-alameda-market/</guid>
      <description>Contact usBook with usSumérgete en la Cultura Colombiana y Saborea los Sabores de Cali a Través de esta Auténtica Experiencia Local de Degustación de Alimentos en el Mercado Alameda.
Degusta las Delicias Culinarias: Bienvenido al tentador Tour Gastronómico en el Mercado Alameda, donde tus papilas gustativas emprenderán un delicioso viaje. En Cali VIP Tours, te invitamos a explorar el rico tapiz de la cocina colombiana, guiado por lugareños que conocen el mercado a fondo.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
