<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Discover the Heartbeat of Cali on Cali VIP Tours</title>
    <link>https://caliviptours.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Discover the Heartbeat of Cali on Cali VIP Tours</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 16:50:00 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://caliviptours.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mural Interventions at Cali Downtown</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/blog/mural-interventions-in-cali/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2023 16:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/blog/mural-interventions-in-cali/</guid>
      <description>Explore Cali&amp;rsquo;s Vibrant Street Art Scene  [Credit: Radiónica]  Today marked the beginning of mural interventions on Calle 5, near the &amp;ldquo;Tunel Mundialista,&amp;rdquo; where an artistic intervention with murals and graffiti commenced today. It involves 42 urban artists from the capital of Valle del Cauca.
Supported by a security detail and traffic precautions to avoid disruptions for drivers using the 500-meter underpass from Avenida del Rio. Five days are scheduled for local artists to express their creativity: September 27th to October 1st, 2023.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explore the Marvels of Cali with VIP Tours!</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 09:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-2/</guid>
      <description>Get ready for an incredible adventure through the vibrant city of Cali! Look no further than Cali VIP Tours – your ultimate companion for delving into the heart and soul of Colombia. Our exceptional tour services are designed to cater to travelers from all around the world, whether you hail from the USA, Europe, Asia, Latinoamerica, or any other corner of the globe. Prepare to be captivated by the charm and excitement that only Cali can offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Cali VIP Blog</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-1/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our blog, your window into the world of Cali VIP Tours. Step into a realm where Cali&amp;rsquo;s vibrant culture, captivating history, and unforgettable experiences come to life.
Our blog is your personal guide to uncovering the richness of Cali, guided by the expertise of Cali VIP Tours. As your companions in exploration, we&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to share insider perspectives, hidden gems, and local insights that illuminate the essence of the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Cali</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 01:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-0/</guid>
      <description>Cali, officially Santiago de Cali, is the capital of Valle del Cauca in Colombia. With over 2.2 million residents, it&amp;rsquo;s the country&amp;rsquo;s third most populous city after Bogotá and Medellín. As the only major Colombian city on the Pacific Coast, Cali is a significant economic hub. It was founded by Spanish explorer Sebastian Belalcázar on July 25, 1536.
 Cali Map| Free WiFi| Cali Consulates| Book with us General Information             Location Southwestern Colombia (Valle del Cauca capitol)   Population About 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Love and Friendship in Cali</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 01:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-3/</guid>
      <description>Cali, the salsa capital of Colombia, is gearing up for a unique celebration of Love and Friendship on September 15, 2023. This Colombian festivity, full of joy and affection, is a perfect opportunity to enjoy the city and share special moments with your loved ones.
Cali is known for its hospitality. During this celebration, the streets will be filled with music, dance, and a festive atmosphere that will make you groove.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Discover the Heartbeat of Cali</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 01:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-4/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to your Cali VIP Tours website, where you can find key information about a vibrant city where culture and the music heartbeat fill the air: Santiago de Cali. We are better every day and offer better services and tours.
Explore Cali&amp;rsquo;s lively streets with us. Feel the passion of dancing, savor the flavors of colombian cuisine, and uncover the hidden gems of this captivating city. Your adventure begins with Cali VIP Tours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another satisfied client</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/testimonials/testimonial-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/testimonials/testimonial-3/</guid>
      <description>
 &amp;ldquo;Has being great! From picking me up on time to bring me to my hotel, show me around all the nice restaurants and bars! Is like having an instant friend here in Colombia&amp;rdquo;.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cali City the CAPTIVATING TOUR</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/tours/cali-city-the-captivating-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/tours/cali-city-the-captivating-tour/</guid>
      <description>Immerse yourself in the rich history and culture of Cali. Explore historic neighborhoods, visit local markets, and savor traditional Colombian cuisine to embark on an extraordinary journey through the heart and soul of this vibrant Colombian city. At Cali VIP Tours, our passion for exploration and discovery knows no bounds.
 Discover San Antonio: Our adventure begins in the enchanting neighborhood of San Antonio. Cobblestone streets lined with colorful houses, adorned with street art, create an atmosphere that&amp;rsquo;s both charming and inspiring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   Cali VIP Tours is a project dedicated to showcasing the essence of Cali in a unique way.
If you would more details, further information, assistance, book a guide tour,or say &amp;ldquo;hello&amp;rdquo;, please use this form.
Go Back</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nice spot</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/testimonials/testimonial-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/testimonials/testimonial-1/</guid>
      <description>
 &amp;ldquo;Unforgettable! Cali VIP Tours provided me with an experience like no other. From the moment I&amp;rsquo;d join their guide, It felt like exploring Cali with a close friend. I recommend then to explore Cali in an authentic and memorable way&amp;rdquo;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Private Salsa Lesson Experience (With Locals)</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/tours/private-salsa-lesson-experience-with-locals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/tours/private-salsa-lesson-experience-with-locals/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the exciting Private Salsa Lesson Experience (With Locals) .Challenge yourself and get to know Cali through its best cultural expression: Salsa! Get your dancing shoes on! The private lessons will have you heart beat.
Immerse in the Hot Rhythm: At Cali VIP Tours, we offer you the chance to dive into the passion and vitality of Salsa, the dance that makes the city&amp;rsquo;s heart beat. Salsa is more than just moves; it&amp;rsquo;s a window into Cali&amp;rsquo;s cultural treasures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Somewhere in Chipichape</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/testimonials/testimonial-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/testimonials/testimonial-2/</guid>
      <description>
 &amp;ldquo;I would definitely go back to Cali again I had an amazing experience, the unique thing about this tour concept is that you don&amp;rsquo;t have a guide, you have a friend that takes you through the real Cali culture. Something that I really like is that depending on your need, they will schedule a tour that fits you the best!&amp;rdquo;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fooding Tour Alameda Market Exploration</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/tours/the-fooding-tour-alameda-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/tours/the-fooding-tour-alameda-market/</guid>
      <description>This is an invitation to exploring Alameda Market in a culinary adventure in the heart of Cali. Nestled in the central neighborhood of Alameda, Alameda Market offers a vibrant and authentic taste of Colombian culture. You are the main guess of this floavor adventure for every taste. Get in on a culinary hub journey in this traditional local borough market.
Savoring colombian delights at Alameda  Explore the rich tapestry of Colombian cuisine: Guided by locals who know the market inside out.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Through Downtown Walking Tour</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/tours/through-downtown-walking-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/tours/through-downtown-walking-tour/</guid>
      <description>Take a leisurely stroll through the heart of Cali, where history and modernity converge. Discover colonial architecture, vibrant street art, lively markets and the singing city: Welcome to the thrilling downtown side tour to catch the refulgent essence of the city that awaits us at every corner.
Cali is always full of color The singing city overthere: Welcome to the thrilling Cali Downtown Walking Tour. At Cali VIP Tours, we are dedicated to providing you with a unique experience that captures the passion and vitality that make Cali an unforgettable destination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to San Cipriano Tour Adventure</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/tours/trip-to-san-cipriano-river-tour-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/tours/trip-to-san-cipriano-river-tour-adventure/</guid>
      <description>Trip to San Cipriano With Cali VIP Tours Explore the enchanting San Cipriano River, one of the most crystal clear water world wide. This eventual tour takes you deep into the heart of the Valle rainforest, where the San Cipriano River weaves its magic. A natural pristine landscapes, encounter diverse wildlife, and take refreshing dips in crystal-clear river waters.
 San Cipriano Tour Adventure Ready for an unforgettable experience? Contact us via WhatsApp in the WhatsApp links around the website,to book your San Cipriano River Adventure with Cali VIP Tours.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Valle and Eje Cafetero Through Coffee Region Panorama</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/tours/trip-to-valle-and-eje-through-coffee-region-panorama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/tours/trip-to-valle-and-eje-through-coffee-region-panorama/</guid>
      <description>Trip to Eje Cafetero Discover the Coffee Paradise and experience safe and comfortable trip as you prepare for an exciting journey through the picturesque coffee region of Colombia. Let us be your companions on journey from and to Cali fot this eventual tour. Enjoy a private transfer to lush coffee farms, where you&amp;rsquo;ll learn the art of coffee production and savor freshly brewed colombian coffee.
 Adventure to Eje Cafetero At Cali VIP Tours, we prioritize your journey&amp;rsquo;s comfort and enjoyment, making every transfer an integral part of your overall experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
