<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cali VIP Tours</title>
    <link>https://caliviptours.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cali VIP Tours</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 09:30:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://caliviptours.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Explore the Marvels of Cali with VIP Tours!</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 09:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-2/</guid>
      <description>Get ready for an incredible adventure through the vibrant city of Cali! Look no further than Cali VIP Tours – your ultimate companion for delving into the heart and soul of Colombia. Our exceptional tour services are designed to cater to travelers from all around the world, whether you hail from the USA, Europe, Asia, Latinoamerica, or any other corner of the globe. Prepare to be captivated by the charm and excitement that only Cali can offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to Cali VIP Blog</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Aug 2023 10:30:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/blog/blog-1/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our blog, your window into the world of Cali VIP Tours. Step into a realm where Cali&amp;rsquo;s vibrant culture, captivating history, and unforgettable experiences come to life.
Our blog is your personal guide to uncovering the richness of Cali, guided by the expertise of Cali VIP Tours. As your companions in exploration, we&amp;rsquo;re thrilled to share insider perspectives, hidden gems, and local insights that illuminate the essence of the city.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Cali</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/about/</guid>
      <description>Cali MapFree WiFiCali ConsulatesBook with usGeneral Information Cali, officially Santiago de Cali, is the capital of Valle del Cauca in Colombia. With over 2.2 million residents, it&amp;rsquo;s the country&amp;rsquo;s third most populous city after Bogotá and Medellín. As the only major Colombian city on the Pacific Coast, Cali is a significant economic hub. It was founded by Spanish explorer Sebastian Belalcázar on July 25, 1536.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cali City the CAPTIVATING TOUR</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/tours/cali-city-the-captivating-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/tours/cali-city-the-captivating-tour/</guid>
      <description>Immerse yourself in the rich history and culture of Cali. Explore historic neighborhoods, visit local markets, and savor traditional Colombian cuisine to embark on an extraordinary journey through the heart and soul of this vibrant Colombian city. At Cali VIP Tours, our passion for exploration and discovery knows no bounds.
Discover San Antonio: Our adventure begins in the enchanting neighborhood of San Antonio. Cobblestone streets lined with colorful houses, adorned with street art, create an atmosphere that&amp;rsquo;s both charming and inspiring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   Cali VIP Tours is a project dedicated to showcasing the essence of Cali in a unique way.
Contact us for further information for assistance and booking:
Book with usGo Back</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dave from England</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/testimonials/testimonial-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/testimonials/testimonial-1/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Unforgettable! Cali VIP Tours provided me with an experience like no other. From the moment I&#39;d join their guide, It felt like exploring Cali with a close friend. I recommend then to explore Cali in an authentic and memorable way&#34;Go Back</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Paul</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/testimonials/testimonial-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/testimonials/testimonial-2/</guid>
      <description>&#34;I would definitely go back to Cali again I had an amazing experience, the unique thing about this tour concept is that you don&#39;t have a guide, you have a friend that takes you through the real Cali culture . Something that I really like is that depending on your need they will schedule a tour that fits you the best!&#34;Go Back</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Private Salsa Lesson Experience (With Locals)</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/tours/private-salsa-lesson-experience-with-locals/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/tours/private-salsa-lesson-experience-with-locals/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the exciting Private Salsa Lesson Experience (With Locals) Challenge yourself and get to know Cali through its best cultural expression: Salsa! Get your dancing shoes on! Learn the sultry moves of Salsa from local experts. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or an experienced dancer, this private lesson will have you makes the city’s heart beat.
Immerse in the Hot Rhythm: Welcome to the exciting Private Salsa Lesson Experience (With Locals), where Cali&amp;rsquo;s fiery rhythm becomes your guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fooding Tour Alameda Market</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/tours/the-fooding-tour-alameda-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/tours/the-fooding-tour-alameda-market/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Cali VIP Tours Experience Colombian Culture and Savor the Flavors of Cali Through this Authentic Local Food Tasting Experience at Alameda Market. Indulge your taste buds on a culinary adventure at the Alameda Market. Sample delicious Colombian dishes, street food, and exotic fruits while exploring this vibrant market.
Taste Culinary Delights: Welcome to the enticing Fooding Tour at Alameda Market, where your taste buds embark on a delicious journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Through Downtown Walking Tour</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/tours/through-downtown-walking-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/tours/through-downtown-walking-tour/</guid>
      <description>Take a leisurely stroll through the heart of Cali, where history and modernity converge. Discover colonial architecture, vibrant street art, lively markets and the singing city: Welcome to the thrilling downtown side tour to catch the vibrant essence of the city that awaits us at every corner.
The Singing City: Welcome to the thrilling Cali Downtown Walking Tour, where the vibrant essence of the city awaits you at every corner. At Cali VIP Tours, we are dedicated to providing you with a unique experience that captures the passion and vitality that make Cali an unforgettable destination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to San Cipriano Tour Adventure</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/tours/trip-to-san-cipriano-river-tour-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/tours/trip-to-san-cipriano-river-tour-adventure/</guid>
      <description>With Cali VIP Tours Explore the enchanting San Cipriano River, one of the most crystal clear water world wide. This tour takes you deep into the heart of the Valle rainforest, where the San Cipriano River weaves its magic. A natural pristine landscapes, encounter diverse wildlife, and take refreshing dips in crystal-clear river waters.
A Natural Paradise
San Cipriano is a hidden paradise, untouched by time. With us, you&amp;rsquo;ll journey through pristine landscapes, encounter diverse wildlife, and take refreshing dips in crystal-clear river waters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trip to Valle and Eje Cafetero Through Coffee Region Panorama</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.com/tours/trip-to-valle-and-eje-through-coffee-region-panorama/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.com/tours/trip-to-valle-and-eje-through-coffee-region-panorama/</guid>
      <description>Experience safe and comfortable travel as you prepare for an exciting journey through the picturesque coffee region of Colombia. Let us be your companions on journey from and to Cali. Enjoy a private transfer to lush coffee farms, where you&amp;rsquo;ll learn the art of coffee production and savor freshly brewed colombian coffee.
Discover the Coffee Paradise: Welcome to the Private Transfer for Coffee Touring Region, where convenience meets exploration. At Cali VIP Tours, we prioritize your journey&amp;rsquo;s comfort and enjoyment, making every transfer an integral part of your overall experience.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
