<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Cali VIP Tours</title>
    <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Cali VIP Tours</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://caliviptours.netlify.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About Us</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/about/</guid>
      <description>About Cali VIP Tours   At the heart of Cali VIP Tours, we find an overflowing passion to uncover the treasures of our city. Our journey began years ago when, exploring every corner of Cali, we discovered the essence that makes it unique: its ANANKE, its unparalleled spirit.
Cali VIP Tours is a project dedicated to showcasing the essence of Cali in a unique way. Our approach takes inspiration from the romantic/gothic novel &amp;ldquo;The Hunchback of Notre-Dame&amp;rdquo; by Victor Hugo, but instead of an ancient cathedral, we focus on Cali&amp;rsquo;s contemporary treasures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anna prado - August 2023</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/testimonials/testimonial-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/testimonials/testimonial-2/</guid>
      <description>Nice to being there!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antoiné Zudeikis - August 2023</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/testimonials/testimonial-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/testimonials/testimonial-3/</guid>
      <description>Very happy went Cali Tour!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cali City Tour</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/cali-city-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/cali-city-tour/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the captivating Cali City Tour, where we invite you to embark on an extraordinary journey through the heart and soul of this vibrant Colombian city. At Cali VIP Tours, our passion for exploration and discovery knows no bounds.
Discover San Antonio: Our adventure begins in the enchanting neighborhood of San Antonio. Cobblestone streets lined with colorful houses, adorned with street art, create an atmosphere that&amp;rsquo;s both charming and inspiring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cali Walking Tour DownTown</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/cali-walking-tour-downtown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/cali-walking-tour-downtown/</guid>
      <description>Let the warm heart of this city conquer you as its music and dance envelop you on this walking tour through Cali&amp;rsquo;s main sites.
The Singing City: Welcome to the thrilling Cali Downtown Walking Tour, where the vibrant essence of the city awaits you at every corner. At Cali VIP Tours, we are dedicated to providing you with a unique experience that captures the passion and vitality that make Cali an unforgettable destination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cali&#39;s Culinary Delights: A Gastro-Adventure with Cali VIP Tours</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/blog/blog-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/blog/blog-2/</guid>
      <description>Cali VIP Tours   Prepare your taste buds for a mouthwatering journey as we dive into the flavors of Cali with Cali VIP Tours. Beyond its vibrant culture and pulsating rhythms, Cali&amp;rsquo;s culinary scene is a treasure trove waiting to be savored.
Savoring Local Flavors  Cali VIP Tours   Our tours aren&amp;rsquo;t just about exploration – they&amp;rsquo;re a passport to Cali&amp;rsquo;s culinary identity. From bustling local markets to hidden gem eateries, our guides know the nooks and crannies where authentic Colombian dishes take center stage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coffee Touring Region Private Transfer</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/coffee-tour-region-private-transfer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/coffee-tour-region-private-transfer/</guid>
      <description>Experience safe and comfortable travel as you prepare for an exciting new adventure. Let us be your companions on journeys to and from Cali, as well as to or from Pereira, Armenia, Salento, or Filandia, in the heart of the coffee region.
Discover the Coffee Paradise: Welcome to the Private Transfer for Coffee Touring Region, where convenience meets exploration. At Cali VIP Tours, we prioritize your journey&amp;rsquo;s comfort and enjoyment, making every transfer an integral part of your overall experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/contact/</guid>
      <description>This is the contact page for.
This is an example of a custom shortcode that you can put right into your content. You will need to add a form action to the shortcode to make it work. Check out Formspree por un simple, servicio de libre forma.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explore the Marvels of Cali with Unmatched VIP Tours!</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/blog/blog-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/blog/blog-1/</guid>
      <description>Cali VIP Tours   Get ready for an incredible adventure through the vibrant city of Cali! Look no further than Cali VIP Tours – your ultimate companion for delving into the heart and soul of Colombia. Our exceptional tour services are designed to cater to travelers from all around the world, whether you hail from the USA, Europe, Asia, Latinoamerica, or any other corner of the globe. Prepare to be captivated by the charm and excitement that only Cali can offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Phil Specktor - August 2023</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/testimonials/testimonial-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/testimonials/testimonial-1/</guid>
      <description>Unforgetable!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Cipriano Tour Adventure</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/san-cipriano-tour-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/san-cipriano-tour-adventure/</guid>
      <description>San Cipriano River Adventure with Cali VIP Tours
Explore the enchanting San Cipriano with Cali VIP Tours. This tour takes you deep into the heart of the Colombian rainforest, where the San Cipriano River weaves its magic.
A Natural Paradise
San Cipriano is a hidden paradise, untouched by time. With us, you&amp;rsquo;ll journey through pristine landscapes, encounter diverse wildlife, and take refreshing dips in crystal-clear river waters.
Book Your Adventure</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fooding Toor Alameda Market</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/the-fooding-tour-alameda-market/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/the-fooding-tour-alameda-market/</guid>
      <description>Immerse yourself in Colombian culture and savor Cali&amp;rsquo;s flavors through this authentic local food tasting experience at Alameda Market.
Taste the Culinary Delights: Welcome to the tantalizing Food Tour in Alameda Market, where your taste buds will embark on a delightful journey. At Cali VIP Tours, we invite you to explore the rich tapestry of Colombian cuisine, guided by locals who know the market inside out.
Discover Alameda Market: Our tour takes you through the vibrant Alameda Market, a hub of activity where locals and visitors alike gather to indulge in the freshest produce, unique ingredients, and mouthwatering dishes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tour 5</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/private-salsa-lesson-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/tours/private-salsa-lesson-experience/</guid>
      <description>Challenge yourself and get to know Cali through its best cultural expression: Salsa! This way, you can dance and mingle with us.
Immerse in the Hot Rhythm: Welcome to the exciting Private Salsa Lesson Experience (With Locals), where Cali&amp;rsquo;s fiery rhythm becomes your guide. At Cali VIP Tours, we offer you the chance to dive into the passion and vitality of Salsa, the dance that makes the city&amp;rsquo;s heart beat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling Cali&#39;s Rhythms: A Salsa Journey with Cali VIP Tours</title>
      <link>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/blog/blog-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://caliviptours.netlify.app/blog/blog-3/</guid>
      <description>Cali VIP Tours   Get ready to move to the beat of Cali&amp;rsquo;s vibrant soul as we take you on an unforgettable Salsa journey with Cali VIP Tours. In the Salsa Capital of the World, rhythm is not just a part of life – it&amp;rsquo;s the heartbeat that fuels the city&amp;rsquo;s energy.
Dancing Through History  Cali VIP Tours   Experience the history of Salsa in its birthplace.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
